gamebillet.com 2016-01-11

# Privacy Policy

  * Your shopping cart is empty!

 **PRIVACY POLICY  **

 **Controllers of Personal Information**

 **Any personal information provided to or gathered by GameBillet.com is controlled by ALDA Y.E.T.T. Limited, 1371 Sokak No 2 Kasman Ismerkezi Kat 5 No503 Izmir Turkey.**

 **What Personal Information About Customers Does GameBillet.com Gather?**

 **The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience at GameBillet.com. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as wish lists and customer reviews and recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our store and platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.**

 **Here are the types of information we gather.**

 **Information You Give Us: we receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.**

 **Automatic Information: we receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses GameBillet.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of GameBillet.com on other Web sites.  **

 **E-mail Communications: to help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from GameBillet.com if your computer supports such capabilities.**

 **Information from Other Sources: we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.**

 **Specific examples include:**

 **Your name**

 **Your address**

 **Your email address**

 **Your phone number**

 **Your credit / debit card details**

 **Your order history and profile**

 **We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.**

 **What About Cookies?**

 **Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to support features such as storage of items in your Shopping Basket between visits. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of GameBillet.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any GameBillet.com products and services that require you to Sign in.  **

 **If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.  **

 **Electronic Communications**

 **When you use any GameBillet Service or send emails to us, you are communicating with us electronically.  We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on the website or through the other GameBillet Services.  For contractual purposes, you consent to receive communications from us electronically and you agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing, unless mandatory applicable laws specifically require a different form of communication.**

 **Does GameBillet.com share the Information it receives?**

 **Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. GameBillet.com shares customer information only as described below and with and the subsidiaries which ALDA Y.E.T.T. Limited controls and that are either subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.**

 **We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties**

 **How Secure Is Information About Me?**

 **We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.**

 **We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.**

 **It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.  **

 **What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites?**

 **Our site may include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.  **

 **These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalise advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.**

 **What Information Can I Access?**

 **GameBillet.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with GameBillet.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.  **

 **What Choices Do I Have?**

 **As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such GameBillet.com features as Your Profile, Wish Lists and Customer Reviews.**

 **If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of GameBillet.com and orders placed with GameBillet.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)**

 **The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of GameBillet.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Basket, proceed to Checkout, or use any GameBillet.com products and services that require you to Sign in.  **

 **Notices and Revisions**

 **If you have any concern about privacy at GameBillet.com, please e-mail us a thorough description and we will try to resolve the issue for you.**

 **Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.**
